Inventory of the Willbur Fisk Papers: Correspondence to Willbur Fisk, 1812 - 1839
Willbur Fisk Papers: Correspondence to Willbur Fisk, 1812 - 1839
- Correspondence to Willbur Fisk
  - Kennedy, William M., 12 April 1832-4 April 1838 (2)
  - Kennon, R. S., 5 June 1835 (1)
  - Kent, Aza, 20 February 1829-4 March 1835 (4)
  - Keteltas, Philip, 16 March 1832 (1)
  - Kiderlen and Stollmeyer, 18 January 1838 (1)
  - King, Dexter S., 7 December 1830-9 January 1839 (8)
  - King, Joseph L., 31 July 1835 (1)
  - King, Rufus T. 26 July 1838 (1)
  - Kingsbury, Benjamin Jr., 5 January 1835-13 August 1834 (3)
  - Kingsley, J. L., 17 February 1832 (1)
  - Kingsley, L. J. D., 2 July 1832 (1)
  - Knight, Joel, 8 December 1838 (1)
  - Knight, Prentiss, 24 January 1833 (1)
  - Knowlton, Marcia, 1827-10 July 1834 (9)
  - Ladd, Azel P., 21 August 1835 (1)
  - Lane, George, 18 August 1831-10 July 1838 (14)
  - Lane, H. B., 5 July 1835-6 July 1837 (3)
  - Langdon, B. F., 5 September 1836-17 July 1837 (5)
  - Larrabee, Artemas B., 5 August 1831 (1)
  - Larrabee, William C., 7 June 1830-20 July 1838 (19)
  - Lathrop, Paoli, 15 October 1834 (1)
  - Laurie, James, 30 March 1835 (1)
  - Law, Andrew, 8 October 1838 (1)
  - Lawrence, J. J. and others, 16 September 1831 (1)
  - Lawrence, Samuel, 23 November 1833-16 September 1834 (4)
  - Lawton, R., 7 October 1836 (1)
  - Leavitt, Joshua, 7 June 1830 (1)
  - Lee, Charles A., 27 May 1833-15 July 1833 (2)
  - Lee, Daniel, 11 January 1836-25 January 1836 (2)
  - Lee, E., 15 July 1832-6 July 1837 (2)
  - Lee, Henry, 16 April 1835 (1)
  - Lee, Luther, 15 August 1835 (1)
  - Leech, Daniel D. T., 17 January 1832-26 January 1833 (2)
  - Leech, Samuel, 24 August 1835 (1)
  - Lehan, L. W., 30 July year unknown (1)
  - Leigh, Jane and Josiah Flournoy, 5 August 1837 (1)
  - Leonard, Joseph, 24 May 1833-26 January 1835 (7)
  - Levings, Noah, 22 October 1834-29 June 1838 (6)
  - Lewis, D. P., 4 May 1835 (1)
  - Lewis, John, 8 June 1831-22 March 1832 (3)
  - Lewis, John W., 30 January 1833-28 June 1837 (4)
  - Lewis, N. C., 1833 (1)
  - Lilly, Wait & Co., 19 December 1832 (1)
  - Lincoln, Timothy D., 19 July 1838 (1)
  - Lindsey, John, 29 August 1824-19 July 1838 (16)
  - Linsley, James H., 19 October 1833 (1)
  - Livesey, W., 12 March 1833 (1)
  - Longacre, James B., 27 December 1837 (1)
  - Loomis, Maria E., 7 March 1833 (1)
  - Lourie, W. F., 9 July 1835 (1)
  - Love, Asa, 14 April 1834 (1)
  - Lovejoy, John, 26 April 1835-9 December 1837 (3)
  - Lovey, John and others, 3 May 1837 (1)
  - Luckey, John, 3 October 1833 (1)
  - Luckey, Samuel, 23 October 1829-9 February 1839 (23)
  - Lugenbeel, James W., 29 May 1837 (1)
  - Lummen, Aaron, 4 December 1830 (1)
  - Lunn, William, 28 April 1837 (1)
  - Lyon, James H., 7 April 1835-11 July 1835 (3)
  - Lyon, Jonathan, 22 December 1837 (1)
  - Lyon, Walter W., 12 August 1835 (1)
  - Lyon, William P. and Charles H., 25 January 1838 (1)
  - McClintock, John, 23 June 1832 (1)
  - McClure, David, 5 October 1836 (1)
  - MacDonald, George Browne, 8 September 1836 (1)
  - Machin, William, 1 October 1836 (1)
  - McKierney, Samuel, 10 August 1831 (1)
  - McKever, Jos. B., 13 October 1837 (1)
  - McKendree, William and others, 25 May 1824 (1)
  - McLaren, William, 16 July 1838 (1)
  - MacReading, C. S., 29 December 1837-13 March 1838 (2)
  - McVickar, John and others, 18 June 1836 (1)
  - Magnuson, Finn, 20 July 1836 (1)
  - Magoun, William, 13 August 1832 (1)
  - Magrender, John B., 6 February 1833 (1)
  - Malcom, Thomas S., 19 December 1838 (1)
  - Maltby, A. D., 17 October 1833 (1)
  - Mankin, George S., 25 April 1833-12 December 1836 (3)
  - Marcy, L., 27 October 1837 (1)
  - Marsden, George, 5 August 1831-12 August 1836 (2)
  - Marsh, Capen and Lyon, November 1838 (1)
  - Marsh, John, 24 May 1833-1 May 1837 (2)
  - Marsh, W. W., 31 January 1838-13 November 1838 (2)
  - Marshall, John G., 20 March 1834-6 March 1835 (5)
  - Martin, George, 3 August 1835 (1)
  - Martindale, Stephen, 20 March 1832-25 November 1836 (4)
  - Marvin, John G., 17 November 1837 (1)
  - Mash, Joseph, 8 August 1833 (1)
  - Mason, M. M., 4 July 1837-13 October 1838 (4)
  - Mason, Thomas, 1 August 1834-10 August 1838 (3)
  - Mason, T. and Love, G., 3 January 1836-22 August 1838 (3)
  - Massey, James A., 17 April 1832-14 April 1834 (2)
  - Mather, W. W., 20 November 1832-4 March 1835 (11)
  - Mathews, J. M., 20 September 1831 (1)
  - Matthias, John J., 29 July 1838-26 October 1838 (2)
  - Mattison, Spencer, 22 February 1834-31 July 1838 (4)
  - Mattison, Thomas J., 10 August 1837 (1)
  - Mattocks, John, 14 October 1834-1 October 1838 (5)
  - May, Samuel J. and others, 19 July 1831 (1)
  - Mead, Benjamin, 7 May 1835 (1)
  - Mead, Ralph, 24 July 1835 (1)
  - Means, A., 16 February 1835 (1)
  - Mercer, Isaiah, 10 March 1832-16 July 1833 (6)
  - Mercer, William F., 4 March 1833-26 June 1834 (4)
  - Merrick, Frederick, 2 January 1837-20 July 1838 (5)
  - Merrill, Ambrose P., 14 April 1832-25 June 1838 (3)
  - Merrill, John W., 31 May 1832-24 August 1835 (5)
  - Merrill, J. A., 9 January 1833-12 June 1838 (9)
  - Merritt, Timothy, 10 June 1824-23 February 1838 (30) (Box 5)
  - Mervin, S., 24 July 1827 (1)
  - Metcalf, David, 18 December 1834-14 January 1835 (2)
  - Miller, Charles R., 19 January 1838 (1)
  - Minor, Thomas, 2 March 1839 (1)
  - Miller, John, 27 October 1837 (1)
  - Miller, John C., 24 April 1838 (1)
  - Miller, Joseph Jr., 30 April 1835 (1)
  - Millington, John, 29 April 1833 (1)
  - Milnor, James, 7 September 1835 (1)
  - Mitchell, A. H., 15 December 1838 (1)
  - Mitchell, James, 1 August 1834 (1)
  - Mitchell, W. G. and others, June 1834-10 November 1838 (3)
  - Montanava, Giovani, May 1836 (1)
  - Montgomery, J., 14 October 1836 (1)
  - Moore, Abraham, 13 July 1830 (1)
  - Moore, E. J., 19 February 1835 (1)
  - Moretz, Andre, 1 October 1835 (1)
    In French.
  - Morris, Calvary, 13 February 1838 (1)
  - Morrison, Joseph, 24 August 1837 (1)
  - Morse, Abner, 4 February 1835 (1)
  - Morse, Timothy and others, 23 May 1835 (1)
  - Moseley, W. R. H., 1 July 1833 (1)
  - Moss, Joshua, 9 August 1836-7 May 1839 (4)
  - Moulton, James T., 2 May 1835 (1)
  - Mudge, Enoch, 28 January 1829-4 April 1829 (2)
  - Mudge, S. H., 17 January 1831 (1)
  - Mundy, Mary, 1 January 1835-4 August 1835 (2)
  - Mundy, Frederick, 10 August 1835 (1)
  - Murphy, Henry C., 28 July 1838 (1)
  - Murphy, Joseph, undated (1)
  - Nast, William, 12 January 1833 (1)
  - Neale, R. H., August 1835 (1)
  - Negus, Charles, 8 December 1828 (1)
  - Newell, Daniel, 1830 (1)
  - Newhall, J., 24 April 1838 (1)
  - Newman, Samuel P., 4 August 1832 (1)
  - Newstead, Robert, 23 January 1836-18 January 1838 (6)
  - Newton, A., Jr., 24 October 1838 (1)
  - Nichols, I. L., 9 February 1831-4 April 1833 (2)
  - Nichols, Jonathan, 4 April 1832 (1)
  - Nitchie, John, Treasurer, 3 October 1837 (1)
  - Nixon, John, 11 August 1837
  - Nollner, Jacob, 26 March 1834-9 June 1838 (7)
  - Norris, Rev. Samuel and others, 13 July 1837-3 September 1838 (3)
  - North, Simeon, 3 January 1833 (1)
  - Norton, John T., 15 August 1836 (1)
  - Ogden, David L., 14 May 1833 (1)
  - Olin, Stephen, 31 December 1834-12 May 1835 (2)
  - Orr, Isaac, 4 April 1832 (1)
  - Osborn, Marcia, September 1824 (1)
  - Osborn, William R., 20 September 1825-29 May 1835 (3)
  - Otis, C. P., 6 April 1835 (1)
  - Otheman, B., 4 January 1833-9 February 1837 (3)
  - Otheman, Edward, 14 January 1831-9 April 1838 (7)
  - Ousely, George, 5 September 1836 (1)
  - Owen, Jacob, 18 February 1836 (1)
  - Owen, John, 22 January 1835 (1)
  - Owen, R., 13 January 1834-9 October 1838 (9)
  - Paddock, B. G., 13 June 1837 (1)
  - Page, J. H. W., 22 May 1833 (1)
  - Paige, L. R., 1 December 1827 (1)
  - Paine, Robert, 24 October 1831-29 October 1831 (2)
  - Palmer, Anthony, 19 May 1833-14 August 1833 (2)
  - Palmer, Marcy, 29 July 1825-10 May 1838 (16)
    Marcy Palmer was Fisk's aunt. 2 letters written with Marcia P. Knowlton.
  - Palmer, Silas, 9 April 1834-11 July 1837 (6)
    Silas Palmer was Fisk's nephew.
  - Palmer, William, 2 April 1835-12 August 1837 (2)
  - Parburt, George R., 15 February 1832 (1)
  - Parker, Ann Thomas, 13 April 1834-20 June 1837 (3)
  - Parker, J., 26 July 1838 (1)
  - Parker, Nancy M., 22 September 1827 (1)
  - Parks, M. P., 11 September 1831-11 January 1834 (4)
  - Parmelee, T. N., 12 June 1838 (1)
  - Parsons, Usher and others, 1 November 1830 (1)
  - Pasco, James Jr., 21 October 1831 (1)
  - Patten, David, 30 August 1831-20 October 1838 (18)
  - Patten, Thomas, 25 May 1830-21 January 1831 (2)
  - Patton, W., 25 December 1834 (1)
  - Patton, W., 19 December 1836 (1)
  - Payne, John Howard, 26 August 1833 (1)
  - Pearsall, J., 21 June 1836 (1)
  - Peasley, James C., 16 January 1831 (1)
  - Peck, George, 13 November 1832-11 August 1838 (12)
  - Peck, Jesse L., 1 April 1837-29 August 1838 (2)
  - Peck, Ruth (Fisk), 18 July 1816-15 June 1838 (22)
    See also Fisk, Ruth (Peck).
  - Perley, Thomas, 9 February 1831 (1)
  - Perry, Salmon, 9 November 1833 (1)
  - Peters, Jesse, 17 September 1837-23 August 1838 (3)
  - Peters, John S., 26 June 1832 (1)
  - Phares, David L., 22 October 1834 (1)
  - Phelps, J. L., 20 March 1832-4 February 1839 (2)
  - Phelps, N. A., 30 July 1835 (1)
  - Phippen, George, 5 March 1831 (1)
  - Pickard, Humphrey, 13 December 1836-10 June 1837 (2)
  - Picket, Albert, 5 July 1838 (1)
  - Pierce, John D., 5 May 1837 (1)
  - Pierce, Lovick, 22 November 1830-21 January 1831 (2)
  - Pikman, Charles, 8 October 1833 (1)
  - Polk, Trusten, 9 October 1833 (1)
  - Porter, Frederick W., 28 August 1833
  - Potter, William H., 16 March 1838 (1)
  - Prandfit, 6 March 1837-21 March 1838 (3)
  - Prescott, William, 4 May 1835-6 March 1837 (5)
  - Prime, Nathaniel S., 12 August 1833 (1)
  - Prindle, Cyrus, 3 August 1831-2 May 1833 (2)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church, a clergyman of, 3 October 1837 (1)
    See Nitchie, John, for item.
  - Purdy, Samuel A., 28 November 1831 (1)
  - Pyre, Smith, 1833 (1)
  - Quincy, Josiah, 18 August 1836-29 October 1837 (2)
  - Ramsdell, H. S., 4 March 1835 (1)
  - Rand, R., 1 February 1838 (1)
  - Randall, George L., 10 April 1838 (1)
  - Randall, Henry, 22 July 1835 (1)
  - Rawson, James, 15 February 1838 (1)
  - Raynor, John, 21 January 1833 (1)
  - Redman, W. W., 13 January 1838-6 August 1838 (2)
  - Reece, Richard, 21 October 1835 (1)
  - Reed, F., 26 July 1832-15 August 1833 (4)
  - Reese, D. M., 7 September 1835-26 June 1837 (4)
  - Remington, E. F., 10 December 1838 (1)
  - Remington, Stephen, 15 August 1834 (1)
  - Renssalaer, B., 1 January 1834 (1)
  - Revell, William Thomas, 1 January 1834-18 January 1836 (2)
  - Rice, Gardner, 3 October 1834-14 June 1838 (3)
  - Rice, J., 15 June 1837 (1)
  - Rice, William, 7 May 1835-7 September 1837 (2)
  - Rich, O., 1 August 1836 (1)
  - Richardson, C., 25 March 1830-26 January 1839 (5)
  - Richardson, Martha G., 12 March 1837 (1)
  - Richardson, Stephen F., 12 January 1838-16 January 1839 (2)
  - Richey, Matthew, 10 July 1838 (1)
  - Ripley, El. W., 15 June 1832-30 July 1833 (3)
  - Robb, John (1)
  - Robbins, Charles, 19 January 1830 (1)
  - Robbins, Eliza, 25 July 1834 (1)
  - Roberts, George C. N. and others, 4 April 1835 (1)
  - Roberts, R. R. and others, 28 May 1836 (1)
  - Robinson, D. J., 27 February 1834-23 May 1834 (2)
  - Robinson, Adam, 21 February 1837 (1)
  - Robinson, Edwin F., 21 December 1836-20 September 1838 (3)
  - Rockwell, S. B., 10 April 1835 (1)
  - Rodman, Thomas P., 17 October 1831 (1)
  - Rogers, C. D., 10 January 1837 (1)
  - Roper, John Jr., 9 September 1834 (1)
  - Ropes, Hardy, 15 October 1832-25 July 1838 (2)
  - Rosser, Leonidas, 25 February 1837 (1)
  - Roud, Aaron, 9 November 1832 (1)
  - Round, George H., 1834-15 October 1838 (8) (Box 6)
  - Rounds, Nelson, 6 April 1835 (1)
  - Rowley, E. A., 21 January 1839
  - Rusling, J., 4 March 1831-12 June 1838 (4)
  - Russell, Samuel, 23 June 1835- 6 July 1838 (5)
  - Rust, Richard S., 1830 (1)
  - Ruter, M., 27 December 1824-17 November 1834 (7)
  - Ryerson, Egerton, 27 November 1828-17 November 1837 (2)
  - Ryerson, John, 27 November 1828 (1)
  - Ryland, William, 30 July 1835 (1)
  - Sanborn, J., 21 September 1832-30 May 1837 (4)
  - Sandford, P. P., 10 July 1828 (1)
  - Sands, John S., 28 September 1829 (1)
  - Sandford, Daniel, 1 March 1838 (1)
  - Sargent, Thomas, 18 April 1831-27 May 1836 (2)
  - Saunders, Turner, 24 August 1829-15 May 1830 (2)
  - Savage, J. A. and Dillon Stevens, 3 July 1837-10 March 1838 (3)
  - Sawyer, Seymour D., 20 August 1833 (1)
  - Sax, R., 17 June 1835-30 June 1835 (2)
  - Schmucher, S. S. and others, 15 January 1839 (1)
  - Scott, Eph., 27 June 1838 (1)
  - Scott, Juliet, 30 April 1832 (1)
  - Scott, J. W., 30 June 1835 (1)
  - Scott, Orange, 26 September 1825-24 October 1838 (5)
  - Scott, William, 1 March 1837 (1)
  - Seager, Schuyler and others, 25 April 1837-17 April 1838 (2)
  - Seammon, I. Young, 2 August 1832 (1)
  - Sewall, Thomas, 21 January 1831-5 May 1838 (24)
  - Sewall, Thomas Jr., 29 September 1837 (1)
  - Sewell, James, 19 April 1838 (1)
  - Seymour, Truman, 4 August 1835-19 December 1838 (2)
  - Seys, John, 11 July 1835-25 June 1838 (2)
  - Shafter, I. M., 20 August 1838 (1)
  - Shafter, William R., 15 October 1827 (1)
  - Sharp, Daniel, 4 September 1835 (1)
  - Sheldon, H. O., 1835 (2)
  - Shepard, Samuel, 28 August 1832 (1)
  - Silliman, B., 6 July 1835 (1)
  - Silliman, Cyrus, 20 September 1831 (1)
  - Simons, Caroline, 19 July 1833 (1)
  - Skinner, A. N., 13 February 1832 (1)
  - Sleeper, Jacob, 6 July 1835-30 June 1838 (2)
  - Sleigh, William, 1836 (1)
  - Smith & Williams, 1835 (1)
  - Smith, Augustus W., 22 May 1831-8 November 1836 (9)
  - Smith, Benj., 10 June 1838-17 June 1838 (2)
  - Smith, B. B., 23 May 1835 (1)
  - Smith, D., 26 July 1831-23 November 1838 (3)
  - Smith, D. B., and W. Hodgson, 31 August 1832-27 September 1832 (2)
  - Smith, Elijha B., 11 August 1838 (1)
  - Smith, Gerritt, 5 March 1835 (1)
  - Smith, John L., 1 February 1838 (1)
  - Smith, J. M., 7 October 1831-10 January 1832 (3)
  - Smith, P. B., 18 December 1838 (1)
  - Smith, Robert L., 13 October 1834 (1)
  - Smith, T., 6 May 1830 (1)
  - Smith, W. A., 1 September 1838 (1)
  - Snead, James M., 25 February 1832 (1)
  - Snow, A. B., 3 November 1828-5 September 1838 (7)
  - Sparks, H. Clark, September 1831 (1)
  - Spaulding, R., 21 September 1837 (1)
  - Speer, Samuel W., 2 August 1838 (1)
  - Spencer, James, 13 June 1838 (1)
  - Sperry, Abe, 30 April 1833 (1)
  - Spicer, T., 19 July 1831-26 June 1837 (6)
  - Spillmann, Hotel, 26 March 1836 (1)
  - Sprague, Ezra, 28 March 1833-27 April 1833 (2)
  - Sprague, Seth Jr., 31 January 1829-1 December 1837 (4)
  - Stanard, Nathan, 19 August 1833 (1)
  - Staples, William R., 18 March 1830-19 June 1835 (2)
  - Stebbins, Lucinda, 15 January 1833 (1)
  - Steele, Allen, 26 January 1832 (1)
  - Steele, Maria, 13 February 1832-28 October 1833 (3)
  - Stevens, A., 24 July 1834 (1)
  - Stevenson, A. C., 1 March 1837-12 April 1837 (2)
  - Stewart, Charles D., 26 June 1830 (1)
  - Stewart, Theophilus, 15 November 1838-11 August 1837 (2)
  - Stewart, William, 12 August 1836 (1)
  - Stibbs, John Thomas, 3 September 1833-4 November 1834 (2)
  - Stinson, Abner, 14 July 1832 (1)
  - Stocking, Selah, 9 February 1831-8 April 1837 (3)
  - Stovall, Ryell P., 12 August 1833 (1)
  - Swingfield, Thomas, 5 February 1835-27 May 1835 (2)
  - Strong, T., 4 May 1835 (1)
  - Stuart, M., 10 April 1837-20 April 1837
  - Suckley, George, 16 May 1832-29 July 1834 (2)
  - Suddards, William, 11 November 1833 (1)
  - Sunderland, LaRoy, 11 February 1832-8 February 1837 (8)
  - Swinburn, John, October 1832-7 November 1838 (7)
  - Tabor, J., 26 September 1836 (1)
  - Taekaberry, Fassey, 20 February 1837 (1)
  - Talbot, M.J., 4 May 1832 (1)
  - Taylor, Moses, 6 March 1831 (1)
  - Templeton, James, 19 February 1829 (1)
  - Terry, David, Jr., 1 June 1837-2 October 1837 (2)
  - Terry, Eliphalet, 11 June 1838 (1)
  - Terry, James, 22 April 1833 (1)
  - Terry, Seth, 3 March 1837 (1)
  - Teubner, B. G. and Claudius F., June 1831 (1)
  - Thacher, William, 17 February 1835 (1)
  - Thayer, L. R., 3 May 1837 (1)
  - Thayer, Stephen H., 17 April 1833-24 April 1833 (2)
  - Thomas, James R., 15 April 1837 (1)
  - Thomas, Susan B., 26 March 1834-July 1837 (5)
  - Thompson, A. C., 7 June 1833 (1)
  - Thornton, Thomas C., 22 March 1838-7 June 1838 (2)
  - Tiffany, C., 6 April 1838 (1)
  - Tifft, Benjamin, 13 August 1835-11 July 1838 (5)
  - Tillinghaut, Charlotte L., 27 October 1825-1828 (2)
  - Tobey, Joseph and Eliza, 30 November 1830-17 January 1836 (2)
  - Tobey, Leonard, 11 April 1833-17 August 1833 (2)
  - Tomlinson, J. S., 17 January 1839 (1)
  - Totten, Silas, 17 May 1837 (1)
  - Townsend, Charles C., 1 August 1832 (1)
  - Tracy, Calvin, 29 July 1838 (1)
  - Tracy, F. P., 18 November 1834 (1)
  - Tracy, Ira, 12 April 1833 (1)
  - True, Charles K., 14 August 1830-27 June 1835 (7)
  - True, Joseph, 22 March 1837 (1)
  - True, William, 4 April 1835-21 April 1835 (2)
  - Turnbull, N. C., 7 February 1837 (1)
  - Turner, Chester W., 20 April 1838 (1)
  - Upham, Thomas, 6 September 1837 (1)
  - Usher, William, 8 June 1831-4 July 1831 (2)
  - Van Normer, D. C., 31 July 1838 (1)
  - Van Slyck, J. M., 1833 (1)
  - Van Valkenburg, John, 16 October 1837-10 January 1838 (2)
  - Veritas, 4 July 1838 (1)
  - Vevers, W., 25 Juoly 1836-22 September 1836 (2)
  - Wakeman, D. E., May 1835 (1)
  - Wakeman, E. B., 20 August 1838-26 October 1838 (2)
  - Wakeman, Jabez, 12 February 1831 (1)
  - Walker, George, 26 August 1837 (1)
  - Walsh, A., 27 June 1838 (1)
  - Ward, Jonathan, 14 June 1837 (1)
  - Waring and Rice, 27 June 1831-12 January 1833 (3)
  - Waterhouse, John, 17 August 1836 (1)
  - Waterman, John A. and David Christy, 19 January 1836 (1)
  - Waters, F., 29 June 1837 (1)
  - Watkinson, John R., 15 August 1833 (1)
  - Watson, Edwin B., 9 July 1835-20 July 1835 (2)
  - Watson, F., 29 June 1835 (1)
  - Waugh, B. and J. Emory, 4 October 1828-1 January 1833 (9)
  - Waugh, Thomas, 14 March 1837-27 April 1837 (2)
  - Way, N. C., 25 July 1838 (1)
  - Way, Townsend, 3 March 1838 (1)
  - Wayland, T., 15 October 1833-2 June 1838 (2)
  - Webster, Ira, 19 September 1837 (1)
  - Webster, Noah, 24 October 1831-13 November 1831 (2)
  - Weed, Nathaniel and others, 3 June 1837 (1)
  - Weeks, S. & S., 12 March 1832-18 December 1833 (3)
  - Weld, Allen, 19 July 1838 (1)
  - Weld, Theodore D., 28 November 1832 (1)
  - Wentworth, Erastus, 27 September 1837 (1)
  - West, William, 30 September 1836 (1)
  - Wheaton, N. S., 2 July 1835 (1)
  - Whedon, D. D., 30 January 1833-4 February 1839 (3)
  - Wheelwright, Joseph, 17 August 1831 (1)
  - Whelpley, S. W., March 1830 (1)
  - White, George, 15 June 1835 (1)
  - White, N., 18 October 1832 (1)
  - Whitehouse, Abraham, 1832 (1)
  - Wickware, Albert G., 1 June 1835-2 April 1838 (2)
  - Wrightman, Stillman R., 22 January 1838 (1)
  - Wilber, P. B., 8 June 1837-11 September 1838 (6)
  - Wilder and others, 5 April 1834 (1)
  - Wiley & Putnam, 1837-1 January 1838 (2)
  - Wilkes, J., 9 March 1838 (1)
  - Willard, J., 18 August 1831 (1)
  - Willard, Paul and Sherman Leland, 23 January 1829 (1)
  - Willett, William M., 30 October 1833-3 February 1834 (2)
  - Williams, Benajah, 8 July 1833 (1)
  - Williams, H. N., 1834-6 April 1835 (7)
  - Williams, James C., 1 June 1831-30 March 1835 (2)
  - Williams, Norman, 2 November 1825-13 October 1826 (2)
  - Williams, Thomas, 24 February 1838 (1)
  - Willing, M. E., 27 June 1835 (1)
  - Willson, S. W., 30 October 1827-19 November 1829 (4)
  - Wilson, J. R., 23 August 1837 (1)
  - Wilson, Sarah, 8 April 1835 and undated (2)
  - Winans, William, 7 July 1832-5 October 1837 (5)
  - Winsor, Lucy, 26 February 1831 (1)
  - Wolcott, James, 24 December 1833 (1)
  - Wood, Daniel B., 28 April 1836 (1)
  - Wood, Felix, 16 July 1837 (1)
  - Wood, Francis A., 26 January 1838-10 July 1838 (2)
  - Wood, Nathan M., 5 July 1837 (1)
  - Woodbridge, W. C., 17 August 1830-25 August 1834 (3)
  - Woodbury, Levi, 9 July 1832 (1)
  - Woodward, George, 29 September 1832-28 December 1833 (2)
  - Woodworth, Nancy, January 1825-7 September 1826 (2)
  - Woolsey, Theodore, 5 November 1831 (1)
  - Worth, Fanning S., 8 March 1837 (1)
  - Wright, 28 February 1838 (1)
  - Wright, Winston and Stebbins, 27 March 1835 (1)
  - Wright, A. H., 11 September 1833 (1)
  - Wright, E. Jr., 18 October 1837 (1)
  - Wright, John F., 16 September 1834 (1)
  - Wright, John L., 3 September 1833 (1)
  - Wright, Simeon, 12 October 1813-3 May 1818 (11)
  - Wurts, Martha H., 2 February 1838 (1)
  - Young, Elbert Anderson, 27 June 1838 (1)